"The Stranger I Met" Episode 7
《我遇见的陌生人》 第7集
(Wu Jindong)
（吴金东）
(Kyung Gi Joo)
（京基珠）
"A Stranger I Met"
《我遇见的一个陌生人》
Did the blue hat show up?
蓝帽子出现了吗？
(past story)
（过去的故事）
there are more people
还有更多的人
- Hersul - Brothers
- 赫苏尔 - 兄弟
That night he fled the bridge
那天晚上他逃离了桥
The blue hat is Bahisu
蓝色帽子是Bahisu
Liu Fan believes
柳范相信
The victim and I walked the same path.
我和受害者走的是同一条路
One of the three current suspects
目前三名嫌疑人之一
a hidden blue hat
一顶隐藏的蓝色帽子
Everything matches the location
一切都与位置相匹配
The person closest to the current defendant
与现任被告关系最密切的人
your father
你父亲
Bais
巴伊斯
I'm talking about blue hat
我说的是蓝帽子
The person who might have killed my mother
可能杀了我母亲的 人
have you seen?
你见过？
I think I can investigate
我想我可以调查
(Bangbang Teahouse)
（邦邦茶馆）
(Section 7 - Overlapping paths)
（第 7 节 - 重叠路径）
Article (7)
第(7)条
Yes
是的
I didn't even know it was wrong from the beginning
我什至不知道从一开始就是错的
1987 Three Suspects
1987 三个嫌疑人
Produced by police who were unable to identify the arresting suspect
由无法确定逮捕嫌疑人的警察 制作的
Find the real culprit from the list of suspects
从嫌疑人名单中 找出真凶
( Suspect in Wu Jong-il serial murder case )
（吴宗日连环杀人案 嫌疑人）
that's wrong
那是错的
How are you?
你还好吗？
I said I can bear it
我说我能忍
Excellent
出色地
Except these two
除了这两个之外
this is not new
这并不新鲜
Although I only found out five minutes ago
虽然我五分钟前才知道
Although Sprite happened
雪碧虽然发生了
Where did you find this photo?
你在哪里找到这张照片的？
This is my first time seeing
我还是第一次见到
Looks like we need to investigate thoroughly
看来要彻底调查一下
Not very good at detective skills
侦探技巧不太好
No
没有
It’s about Bayusu
是关于巴渝苏的
Among so many documents, there is no one
这么多文档中 没有一个
I don't think I'm a suspect
我不认为我是嫌疑人
What kind of person have you become?
你成为了什么样的人？
your great uncle
你的曾叔叔
Bayusu
巴玉素
I have no idea
我不知道
Even though I thought I knew
尽管我以为我很了解
Until today I see you there
直到今天我在那里见到你
(disco)
（迪斯科）
Too far away to call family
太远了，无法给家人打电话
People who are too close cannot be called strangers
太亲近的人不能被称为陌生人
but...
但...
That disappointingly familiar face
那张熟悉到令人失望的脸
there is almost nothing there
那里几乎没有什么
What are you doing now, uncle?
你现在在做什么呢，叔叔？
Book
书
Didn't you tell me not to enter other people's rooms?
你不是叫我不要进别人的房间吗？
Why are you doing this to me?
你为什么这样对我？
- Almost let it go - Haha
- 差不多就放手了 - 呵呵
- Nothing happened - Oops
- 什么都没发生 - 糟糕
(small door)
（小门）
Apologize
道歉
excuse me
打扰一下
Don't shout
别喊
we are family
我们是家人
my father's family
我父亲的家人
Didn’t my mother and I have a place in it from the beginning ?
我和妈妈不是从一开始就在其中占有一席之地吗 ？
Do you think you don’t know enough?
你觉得你还不够了解吗？
That's why this isn't family to me, Dad
这就是为什么这对我来说不是家庭， 父亲
Hey Yoon Young
嘿尹英
hold on..
坚持，稍等..
I do not know
我不知道了
Do I really know that person?
那个人真的是我认识的吗？
What kind of nation has it become?
变成了一个什么样的民族呢？
(Badminton eight events)
（羽毛球八项）
So you have to find out from here
所以你必须从这里找出
I was shocked
我吓了一跳
- Bamboo - Come on
- 竹子 - 来吧
From now on, I will ask three or four very simple questions
从现在开始， 我会问三四个非常简单的问题
If there is a lie in the answer
如果答案中有谎言
There is a parent-teacher meeting tomorrow morning
明天早上有家长 会
it's not fair
这不公平
Parent-teacher conference teacher...
家长会老师..
- Uncle totally ...
- 叔叔完全 ...
Whose is that?
那是谁的？
Is this a hat?
这是帽子吗？
Not yet, the Night King is coming for him
还没有， 夜王来找他了
Why do other people's hats...
为什么别人的帽子..
Will they do it tomorrow?
他们明天会做吗？
I called my uncle at eight o'clock in the morning.
早上八点我给叔叔打了电话。
Why my brother?
为什么是我弟弟？
I rented it for a while last night and watched it.
昨晚租了一段时间看了
last night..
昨夜..
What is the real reason why he went to Wuzhen Inn Alley ?
他去乌镇客栈巷 的真正原因是什么？
Wait, I already said that
等等，我已经说过了
every time i go for a walk
每次我去散步
If I'm wrong I'll ask more specifically
如果我错了， 我会更具体地询问
last night..
昨夜..
Until you change the direction of travel
直到你改变前进的方向
Who asked you to take that path?
谁要求你走那条路的？
The person who walked together but disappeared alone
那个一起走却独自 消失的人
Just like walking out from in front of me
就像从我面前走出来一样
There is no point in lying
说谎的人毫无意义
Who is that?
那是谁？
Please do not turn on the lights on the second floor
二楼请勿开灯
Just confirm
只需确认一下
WHO？
WHO？
Who asked you to do this?
谁要求你这么做的？
Who is your own mouth?
谁是你自己的嘴？
mine..
我的..
brother
兄弟
everything has been paid for
一切都已付出代价
Go to the second floor room where Lee Joo-young is alone at the match shop
到火柴店李周英独自一人的 二楼房间
Do you want to know?
你想知道吗？
Last night, Lee Joo Young didn't even show up at Bom Bom Play House
昨晚，李周英甚至没有出现在 Bom Bom Play House
forced to do this
被迫这样做
This means that Lee Joo Young was targeted from the beginning.
这意味着李柱英从一开始就被针对了
Not that, but here
不是那个，而是这里
The man ran away
男子逃跑了
Below is Lee Joo Young
下面是李柱英
Could it be that he was peeping and escaping at the same time?
难道他是一边偷看一边 逃跑的？
owner of blue hat
蓝帽子的主人
The culprit is Bayusu
罪魁祸首是巴尤苏
If you were in front of such power, you would feel dizzy
如果你在这样的力量面前， 你会感到头晕目眩
If Ba Yusup is the real culprit
如果Ba Yusup是真正的罪魁祸首
No need to wait, see you tomorrow night
不用等， 明晚再见
second victim
第二个受害者
Because you have to kill
因为你必须杀人
Do you really have the confidence to face it yourself?
你真的有信心自己去面对吗？
I mean, there's no need to suppress this feeling.
我是说没必要强行压抑这种感觉
It must be tiring and painful
肯定又累又痛苦
Because after all, we are family
因为毕竟是家人
I'm disgusted, my heart is in chaos
我很厌恶 我的心已经混乱了
but before that
但在那之前
The rest of my thoughts
剩下的我的心思
my mother
我的母亲
And you..
你呢..
There is only one thing that must be protected from despicable people
只有一件事必须保护，免受卑鄙之人的侵害
that's why
这就是为什么
Why not spread the word around the neighborhood?
为什么不把这个消息传遍整个街区呢？
About me and my mother
关于我和我的母亲
I'm just a little confused .
我只是有点困惑 。
No one knows better than me
没有人比我更了解
Required Documents Missing Information
所需文件 缺失信息
From now on I'll fill in everything you need
从现在开始我会填写你需要的一切
from now on
今后
You never know what you'll find
你永远不知道你会发现什么
Do you really have faith?
你真的有信仰吗？
Yes
是的
(trash can)
（垃圾箱）
Who did what?
谁做了什么？
If it were true I would know
如果这是事实我就会知道
Won't run away at all
根本不会逃跑
because it can be protected
因为它可以被保护
Are you there yet?
你到了吗？
Yes
是的
Bring a change of clothes
带上换洗衣物
What to do now?
现在该怎么办呢？
i have to find out
我必须找出答案
Start with who the second victim is.
从第二个受害者是谁开始
who is it?
是谁？
Hello
你好
Contestant No. 2
二号参赛者
Ms. Gyeonggi
京畿女士
Li Jing'e
李京娥
please help
请帮忙
impossible
不可能的
Have you really not noticed something?
难道你真的没有注意到一点吗？
I found my absent aunt
我找到了不在场的阿姨
because of physical weakness
因为身体虚弱
I only know that he died young due to illness
我只知道他因病早逝
Is there anything else that hasn’t been said yet?
还有什么事情还没说完吗？
Already displayed on the second floor
二楼已经展示了
this explains everything
这说明了一切
Do you have any plans this time?
这次你有计划吗？
Rented the house opposite
租了对面的房子
Do you think this is a coincidence?
你认为这是巧合吗？
Everything starts from scratch...
一切从头开始..
Judging from the results for the entire month
从整个月的结果来看
Today will be the most difficult day
今天将是最困难的一天
Because the people we want to save are not ordinary people
因为我们要救的人不是普通人
(University Entrance Examination)
（大学入学考试）
(10,000 won)
(万韩元)
Find Dad's Emergency Fund
找到爸爸的应急基金
I should have thought about it earlier
我应该早点 考虑的
Yes, you can get it if you save a little more
是的，如果你多存一点，你就可以得到它
Just a little more
只要多一点点
Nickname Wu Zongri is crazy
昵称 吴宗日 疯狂
The craziest crazy woman around
附近最疯狂的疯女人
Why are you doing what you are doing?
你为什么在做什么？
It is impossible to understand with normal thinking
用正常思维是无法理解的
that's why it's the front of the house
这就是为什么它是房子的前面
Because I don't know what to do
因为我不知道该怎么办
At that time, the police found the route
当时，民警找到了 该路线
It's hard to believe
很难相信了
Missed too much
太多的错过
After what happened last night, I am even more sure
经过昨晚的事后 我更加确定了
ah
啊
Mother
母亲
Anyway, that's where those guys ended up
无论如何，那是那些人 最后找到的地方
Bom Bom Ti House tonight at 9pm
今晚九点 Bom Bom Ti House
Same as Lee Joo Young
和李周英一样
I must have seen the defendant after I left there
我离开那里后 肯定见过被告
Today is different
今天不一样了
Because we will be behind him
因为我们会在他身后
This time for sure
这次肯定
I will definitely do this
我一定会这么做
our school
我们的学校
What
什么
fever..
发烧..
39 degrees
39度
Yeah, what should I do because I'm the only guardian
是啊，我怎么办呢 ，因为我是唯一的监护人
Of course, if something goes wrong at school now, I have to go to the hospital as soon as possible
当然，如果现在在学校出了问题， 我得尽快去医院
Do you know that hospital at the intersection?
你知道路口那家医院吗？
You don’t have to worry about class at all
完全不用担心上课的问题
Stay connected and take care of yourself
保持密切联系并照顾好自己
Well, yes, yes
嗯，是的，是的
Mother
母亲
Not today
今天不行
You can get it if you go to the hospital
如果去医院就可以得到
Oh, I'm on my way
哦，我在路上
So kids are better off?
那么孩子们就更好了？
Yes, I can be discharged
是的，我可以出院了
I was asked to stay one more day
我被要求多留一天
Great, great
太棒了，太棒了
Take this opportunity to let the kids eat whatever they want.
趁这个机会，让孩子们想吃什么就吃什么。
Let them see their father's face as they please
让他们随心所欲地看到父亲的面容
- Mr. Chairman, why are you doing this? - Take it.
- 主席先生，你为什么要这么做 - 接受吧
if i don't
如果我不这样做
I didn’t dare to look at my son’s face for three or four days.
三四天 不敢看儿子脸
curry
咖喱
It hangs you up so you can't walk
它把你吊起来，所以你不能走
Am I not?
我不是吗？
Didn't do it on purpose
不是故意这样做的
Excellent
出色地
cherry flavor
樱桃味
Has Yin Yu returned to Korea now?
尹宇现在回韩国了吗？
Well, the call came
嗯，电话来了
He will come back to see his father's face
他会回来看他父亲的脸
It's been three years
已经三年了
When slime appears before your eyes, think of it as gratitude
当粘液出现在您眼前时， 请把它视为感激之情
They won't spend the rest of their lives in your arms like children.
他们不会像孩子一样在你的怀里度过余生
Yes
是的
Want to eat one?
吃一个吗？
Oh yes, thank you
噢，是的，谢谢
Really?
真的吗？
If I were a Korean wife, I would buy a fur coat
如果我是韩国太太， 我会买一件皮草大衣
Mother
母亲
Is this a child?
这是一个孩子吗？
Is a fur coat affordable for everyone?
皮草大衣是每个人都买得起的吗？
No compulsory purchase
不强制购买
- I will buy - Madam
- 我会买 - 女士
If only my mother were a Korean lady
要是我妈妈是韩国夫人就好了
Don't cheat and try to stop drinking
不要作弊并 尝试戒酒
Miss Korea
韩国小姐
- I was rude to my sister. - It's okay.
- 我对我妹妹无礼 - 没关系
What about everything that happened to me?
我身上发生的一切怎么样？
In other words, I definitely have potential
也就是说，我绝对 有潜力
Talking about 500,000 won again makes me sick
再谈50万韩元 我就恶心
It's not like you meet someone you don't know
这并不是说你遇到了陌生的人
My mother said she didn't know
我妈说她不知道
But can you support me a little bit?
但你能稍微支持一下我吗？
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
not a penny
一分钱都没有
Can't we hire a math teacher?
不能请数学老师吗？
I can't catch up now
我现在追不上
Now the college entrance examination is approaching
现在高考临近了
If you add a little more to my savings...
如果你再给我的积蓄多加一点..
It doesn't matter
没关系
he is
他是
What should I do when I don't recognize this shadow?
当我不认识这个影子时该怎么办
Sun E
孙鄂
If I had extra money, I would definitely hire a teacher
如果我有多余的钱，我一定会请一位老师
father is late
父亲迟到了
Goodbye my daughter
走好我的女儿
Of course I have to buy some mother and son books
当然，我得买一些母子书
If that's not enough, say it again
如果这还不够，请再说一遍
don't tell your sisters
别告诉你的姐妹们
want to go
要去
Neither noticed nor missed
既没有察觉也没有错过
I said I work in a hair salon
我说我在发廊工作
So are you going to work?
那么你要去工作吗？
I lost my job without notice over something as simple as that.
就这么简单的事情， 我在不通知的情况下丢了工作
There is no record of what he did during this period
没有记录显示他在此​​期间做了什么
You will know if you follow me in the future
以后关注你就知道了
Quiet
安静
Do you have
有没有
Hey Shan'e, did you do this on purpose?
嘿善娥， 你是故意的吗？
What am I doing?
我在做什么？
Just because you think my dreams are interesting
只是因为你觉得我的梦很有趣
Interrupting and talking about you like this
就这样打断并谈论你
Don't spend your money where there is no such hope
不要把钱花在没有这种希望的地方
Use it on my smart girl, don't you think?
用在我聪明的女孩身上， 你说是吗？
I'm sorry to bother you
我很抱歉打扰
I really don’t know because I didn’t listen to my sister
我真的不知道， 因为我没有听姐姐的话
Don't listen...
别听..
Now I'm going to ignore this ratio
现在我要忽略 这个比率
No, that doesn't mean
不， 这并不意味着
Hey, you're good at it, remember?
嘿， 你很擅长，你还记得吗？
that clip
那个剪辑
that's what i'm worried about
这就是我担心的
My dad only bought you one
我爸只买了你一个
Why is the whole school Level 1?
为什么全校都是一级？
So I was loved
于是我就被爱了
Until then, you know what?
到那时，你知道吗？
Do you think my father doesn’t accept you as a teacher because he really has no money?
你以为我父亲 不收你当老师是因为他真的没钱吗？
What's that word?
那个词是什么？
you..
你..
My father had no intention of sending me to college
我父亲并没有送我上大学的想法
How did my sister know?
我姐姐怎么知道的？
You're the only one who doesn't know
你是唯一不知道的人
What was the father's wish from the beginning?
父亲从一开始的愿望是什么？
you and me
你和我
Marry into a good family early
早点嫁入好家庭
I want not to get a drop of water on my hands
我想手上不沾一滴水
After requesting ABO study
要求奥博学习后
I want to find a good job and stay
我想找到一份好工作并留下来
these two wishes
这两个愿望
but you are not like that
但你不是那样的
That's it
就是这样了
Will my sister do the same?
我妹妹也会这样吗？
- What - just like my father.
- 什么 - 就像我父亲那样
I'm not like that
我不是那样的
You can write without taking classes
不用上课也能写
If my sister needs to do this too
如果我姐姐也需要这样做
use this or fill it out
使用这个或填写它
I never thought this was funny
我从没想过这很有趣
Are you reading this to be smart or what?
你读这篇文章是为了聪明还是什么？
I ignored it until the end
我到最后都忽略了
(10,000 won)
(万韩元)
ha
哈
I am angry
我很生气
I can go alone
我可以一个人去
It is not
它不是
Now I wish my mom would follow this direction
现在我希望我妈妈能遵循这个方向
(pay phone)
（付费电话）
This is the first time I resent my grandfather
这是我第一次怨恨我的爷爷
This is my mother's lifelong wish
这是我母亲一生的愿望
In the end I failed to go to college
最后我没能上大学
This was not unusual at the time
这在当时并不罕见
Caste pain is not common
种姓痛苦 并不常见
It means I don’t know enough
说明我还不够了解
How will you feel about blocking your daughter's choice later?
稍后你会对阻止你女儿的选择 有何感想
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
no matter what you do
不管你做什么
We just wait for the defendant to come out
我们就等被告出来
No more changes can be made
无法再进行任何更改
kakao
卡卡奥
Hello
你好
How are you, beautiful?
你好吗，美丽的？
finally ready
终于准备好了
So what are they?
那么它们是什么？
What should happen?
应该发生什么？
Friends who are preparing for the Miss Korea competition with you
和你一起备战韩国小姐比赛的朋友们
He will first conduct South Chora
他将首先进行南乔拉
He is the greatest ancient
他是第一大古
Gyeongbuk Region 3rd place
庆北地区 第三位
I gave 500,000 to make the second one
我给了50万 做第二个
Oh, sorry for the second time
噢，抱歉第二次了
Now
现在
our handsome guy
我们的帅哥
Where will Gyeonggi Province take it?
京畿道将把它带到哪里？
second
第二
Second or first?
第二还是第一？
Enter now
现在输入
hurry up
赶快
let's go
我们走吧
(Wanted for fraud)
（因诈骗罪被通缉）
up
向上
What are you doing I do not have time. hurry up
你在做什么？我没时间。 快点
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
As expected, today is the day I was deceived.
果然今天是被骗的日子
Am I being scammed or something?
我被骗了还是怎么的？
about half a million
约五十万
They will make me Miss Korea
他们会让我成为韩国小姐
- Come on - From the day I first came here
- 来吧 - 从我第一次来到这里的那天起
they improvise
他们即兴发挥
Even if you get money out of it
即使你中间得到了钱
Because I spent all my money on booze and cash
因为我把所有的钱都花在了酒和现金上
No money to cheat
没钱骗
That money is my mother's money
那些钱是我妈妈的钱
I can not afford it
我买不起
Why can't you afford it?
怎么买不起啊？
500,000 tuition fees?
50万学费？
Did you grow up in a wealthy family or were you an only child?
你是在富裕家庭长大还是 独生子？
I don't know because I don't live as a daughter
我不知道，因为我不是作为女儿生活的
That's why I can be so calm
这就是为什么我可以如此平静
what are you talking about?
你到底在说什么？
If you give it back, this won't happen
如果你还给它，就不会发生这种情况
Mom, what happened suddenly?
妈妈，突然发生什么事了？
We must go to Seoul together as soon as possible
我们必须尽快一起去首尔
No matter what happens
不管发生什么
There is a child in our family. He is stupid but very smart.
我们家有一个孩子，他很笨，但 很聪明
Because I worry about him sometimes
因为我有时会担心他
Next year, he will be admitted
明年，他将被录取
I will participate in the competition next year
到时候我 明年就参加比赛
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
- Haha- No way
- 呵呵 - 没办法
What are you doing hurry up
你在做什么？快点
- Ah - this guy
- 啊 - 这家伙
hehe
呵呵
strength
力量
really quiet
真的很安静
hehe
呵呵
- Ha - Wait a minute.
- 哈 - 等等
- Call Kyung Yi first - Yeah.. Daw Lay Ray
- 先打电话给庆伊 - 是的.. Daw Lay Ray
- Mom - Where have you been?
- 妈妈 - 你去哪儿了？
Mom, try to let go
妈妈，试着放手
The bastard who pays back the money
还钱的混蛋
Hey, this girl...
嘿，这个女孩..
hehe
呵呵
Mother
母亲
- Ha - Really
- 哈 - 真的
- Sun Lane - Hen
- 太阳巷 - 母鸡
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
I don't ask because I think it would be difficult
我不问，因为我觉得这会很困难
I really want to know
我真的很想知道
How recently have you moved to school ?
您最近搬到学校多久了 ？
let's be friends
我们成为 朋友吧
only when we feel comfortable with each other
只有当我们彼此感到舒服时
Yes or no
是不是
you are right
你是对的
the person I like
喜欢的人
love at first sight..
一见钟情..
But you know the result
但你知道结果
Even when he opened up, he was rejected
即使他敞开心扉，也被拒绝了
someone is hanging out
有人在闲逛
He doesn't accept my feelings
他不接受我的感受
This guy is honest
这家伙很诚实
thanks for letting me know
谢谢你让我知道
What?
什么？
Ah, why?
啊，为什么？
ha
哈
- Should I pay for anything?
- 我应该付钱 给什么吗？
- Do I have to pay? - What?
- 我要付钱吗 - 什么？
What will you give?
你会给予什么？
Can I get you a sundae?
我给你一杯圣代好吗？
What
什么
just kidding
只是在开玩笑
How are you?
你还好吗？
Are you still affected?
你还受影响吗？
Why now, why start now?
为什么现在， 为什么从现在开始？
This is not a place to meet
这不是见面的地方
If you knew it was me who was chasing you that night
如果你知道那天晚上追你的是我
Ba Yusup is not in this situation, except...
Ba Yusup 并不处于这种情况，除了..
Because of me?
是因为我吗？
Because of Li Jing'e?
因为李京娥？
So this is something that has or has not happened before
所以这是 一个以前发生过或没有发生过的事情
Is this a new problem?
这是一个新问题吗？
We are fine, how are you?
我们很好， 你还好吗？
Thanks
谢谢
I don't think it's easy to get into
我认为进入并不容易
I thought I was passing by by accident and I should do something to help.
我以为不经意路过 应该做点什么帮忙
Don't you think so?
你不这么认为吗？
Yes
是的
I did something big
我做了一件大事
Everyone, wait here for a moment
大家在此稍等片刻
I just went to the police station to report
我刚刚去警察局报到
How did this happen?
这怎么发生的？
Scammers also pass by here...
骗子还路过这里..
catch them all
把他们全部抓住
There is also the possibility of human trafficking
也存在人口贩卖的可能性
i will understand
我会明白的
I think it's a detective
我觉得是侦探
- Let's go. - Of course.
- 我们走吧 - 当然
- Not a detective? - police?
- 不是侦探吗？ - 警察？
- Police - Can you help us?
- 警察 - 你能帮助我们吗？
- They took our money - Yeah.
- 他们拿走了我们的钱 - 是的
- Can you take me home ?
- 你能送我回家 吗？
- Please - No
- 拜托 - 不
- Mom will kill me. - Help me get home.
- 妈妈会杀了我 - 帮我回家
- Please help me
- 请 帮我
- Mom will be angry - What will they do?
- 妈妈会生气 - 他们会怎么做？
- Call my mom - please
- 打电话给我妈妈 - 请
- Mom - I have to go home.
- 妈妈 - 我得回家了
- If you don't call, you'll die - Ha
- 如果你不打电话，你就会死 - 哈
Did they really disappear together?
他们真的一起 消失了吗？
Last night we...
昨晚我们..
Remember how I told you what to do if you had to?
还记得我如何告诉过您在必须 这样做的情况下如何做吗？
yes, I remember
是的，我记得
so be careful
所以要小心
if it is true
如果真的是的话
Although there is absolutely no such thing
虽然绝对不存在这样的事情
if anything changes
如果有任何改变
if you miss the victim
如果你想念受害者
Well
唔
Yes
是的
How are you?
你还好吗？
Unusual, stop immediately
不一般， 马上就停止
come over
过来
did you sleep well?
你睡得好吗？
As far as I know, no
据我所知，没有
Does it matter?
这重要吗？
It is said that the most abundant sad drama in the world is
据说世界上最丰富的是 悲伤剧
Why are you doing so much?
你为什么要做这么多？
Everyone is a stranger to you, right?
每个人对你来说都是陌生人，不是吗？
If you can save everyone, you can't survive
如果你能拯救所有人， 你就无法生存
Just find the culprit
只要找到罪魁祸首
Easier and cheaper way
更简单、更便宜的方式
I think no matter how many there are
我觉得无论有多少
The ground is cold
地面很冷
(3 months in 2022)
（2022 年 3 个月）
When I first learned of my death and went looking for it
当我第一次得知我的死讯并去寻找它时
All conditions are met
所有条件均已满足
three months
三个月
The murder happened two months ago
凶杀案发生在两个月前
Because the destination that can be decided is only one year
因为可以决定的目的地只有一年
If you want to meet the defendant there
如果您想在那里会见被告
There is nothing to do but wait
除了等待，别无他法
Until he comes back a month later
直到一个月后他回来
A whole ten months
整整十个月
No matter what, people die once in a while
无论如何，人 偶尔都会死一次
This is a very bad ending
这是一个非常糟糕的结局
There at that time
那个时候那里
By chance he found a garbage man
碰巧他发现了一个垃圾工
Because everything ended in an instant
因为一切都在一瞬间 结束了
(Bangbang Teahouse)
（邦邦茶馆）
The weather is cold
天气很冷
lie down like abandoned
像被遗弃一样躺下
But such a person
但这样的人
After realizing there is more elsewhere
意识到其他地方还有更多之后
Then I got scared
然后我就害怕了
Because I can't stop it because I know
因为我无法阻止因为我知道
know means change
知道意味着改变
That is..
那是..
Because that's a pretty heavy expectation
因为这是一个相当沉重的期望
Responsible for where Bayusu can be found
负责可以找到Bayusu的地方
how about you?
那么你呢？
I 'll go where the murders actually happened
我 会去真正发生谋杀的地方
(Mysterious murder case, the body was found with its hands and neck tied)
（神秘谋杀案， 尸体被发现时手和脖子都被绑住）
(Another female body was found, a 20-year-old female was killed)
（又发现一名女性尸体， 一名20岁女性被杀）
(Sun and Moon Record Store)
（日月唱片店）
what does that mean?
这意味着什么？
do you know?
你知道吗？
I just wish I hadn't found it
我只是希望我没有找到它
(20-year-old college student was found murdered)
（20岁大学生 被发现被谋杀）
( The body of a school teacher was found on the bank of a river in a quiet village )
（在一个宁静的村庄的河岸上 发现了一名学校老师的尸体）
That is..
那是..
This must mean it's too late
这一定意味着为时已晚
(Wuzhuang Grocery Store)
(五庄杂货店)
Think it's too late?
觉得太晚了吗？
I haven't found any clues yet
我还没有找到任何线索
not enough
还不够
So where exactly are you doing?
那么 你到底在哪里做什么？
all roads and roads
所有的道路和道路
Yes
是的
I don't know if I'm doing something
我不知道我是否在做某事
If nothing really happened
如果真的什么都没发生
Could it be doing something somewhere?
它可能在某个地方做某事吗？
But we can get a good end result
但我们 可以得到一个很好的最终结果
Don't you think I'm just looking for a place like this?
你不觉得我只是在寻找这样的地方吗？
Just enough place to kill someone
刚好够杀人的地方
If Bayusu and I are together, I'm sure...
如果我和Bayusu在一起的话，我确信..
No
不
If so, the field would be very broad
如果是的话，领域会很广
what time is it now?
现在几点了？
9 hours and 10 minutes
9小时10分钟
Ordinary shop
普通屋
This was the last location recorded by police
这是警方记录的最后一个位置
things have changed
情况已经改变
- No reason to go there now.. - No reason not to go there.
- 现在没有理由去那里.. - 没有理由不去那里
I know I'm afraid of change
我知道我害怕改变
I have no idea
我不知道
No matter what you do, the result is the same.
无论你做什么，结果都是一样的。
Such problems often exist
经常存在这样的问题
- That's what time is
- 时间就是这样
I don't even know this is time, this is love
我什至不知道这是时间，这是爱
It's a feeling hidden like fog
是一种像雾一样隐藏的感觉
This is love that shines like the morning star
这是像晨星一样闪耀的爱
Yesterday too
昨天也是
- It was all yesterday
- 昨天都是
Today too
今天也是
- Today - Today all
- 今天 - 今天都
Tomorrow too
明天也有
- I can't stand the entrance being closed - all the time
- 我无法忍受入口被关闭 - 总是
- That's what I want to hear - Please sit down quickly
- 这就是我想听的 - 请快点坐下
- Let's sing I like you together - I like you
- 我们一起唱我喜欢你 - 我喜欢你
bamboo
竹子
- you like me
- 你喜欢我
I want to say this every day
我每天都想说这句话
heart-warming moments
令人心潮澎湃的时刻
If you don't understand, let's sit down
如果你不明白，我们快坐下
This is the love we can share with each other
这是我们可以彼此分享的爱
You like me and I like you too
你喜欢我， 我也喜欢你
Is Gominsu also on the suspect list?
Gominsu也在嫌疑人名单上吗？
He was imprisoned as a defendant for more than thirty years
他作为被告被监禁了三十多年
Although he ultimately refused
虽然他最终拒绝
Is that Ge Minsu?
那是戈敏苏吗？
Why and how?
为什么以及如何？
Although there were three or four witnesses
虽然有三四个证人
The main decision is the witness
主要决定是目击者
He said he witnessed the murder
他说他亲眼目睹了谋杀案
My sister, Wu Xu
我的妹妹，五须
The Wuguang I know?
我认识的那个五光？
One of the two must be lying
两者之一 必定在说谎
At least tonight is for sure
至少今晚是肯定的
Whose words are true?
谁的话是真的？
- Sing another song - Okay
- 唱另一首歌 - 好的
they are breaking up
他们要分手了
( Suspect in Wu Jong-il serial murder case )
（吴宗日连环杀人案 嫌疑人）
I will go find my mother
我会去找我妈妈
Now suddenly?
现在突然？
Go on tell me who's lying
继续告诉我谁在说谎
Li Jing'e
李京娥
our little aunt
我们的小阿姨
I must
我必须
Now we enter the second round
现在我们进入第二轮
- Let's go.
- 我们走吧
GR8
GR8
- always the best - thank you
- 永远是最好的 - 谢谢
Where are they going?
他们要去哪？
(Bangbang Teahouse)
（邦邦茶馆）
This guy..
这家伙..
let's go
我们走吧
ah
啊
- I have to go
- 我得走了 - 我走了
- I'm leaving - Tarta
- 塔尔塔
- Will you come back? - See you tomorrow
- 你会回来吗？ - 明天见
- Gone - Tata
- 走了 - 塔塔
strength
力量
(Bangbang Teahouse)
（邦邦茶馆）
How far do you want to go?
你要走多远？
Because I have something to say
因为我有话要说
(hostel)
（旅馆）
Where did Li Zhuying go in the end?
李珠英最后去哪儿了？
What did he do?
他做了什么？
(hotel entrance)
(宾馆入口)
What's your job?
你做什么工作？
if you have something to say
如果你有话要说
if they break up
如果他们分手了
I know, I will do what you want
我知道，我会如你所愿
So you want to surrender to me too
所以你也想屈服于我
Hey yubum
嘿尤布姆
I have to break up without doing anything.
我什么都不做就必须分手
I'm too good to be immune
我太好了，无法幸免
In the meantime I give you the time
在此期间我给你的 时间
Yes or no
是不是
release
发布
save me, save me
救救我，救救我
hehe
呵呵
Let's go somewhere and have another drink
我们去个地方 再喝一杯吧
They said they wanted to sit at the same table
他们说要坐在同一张桌子上
What do your friends think of me?
你的朋友觉得我怎么样？
Because other friends just sit there for a while
因为其他朋友就坐一会儿
I don't deal with garbage like you
我不会像你一样处理垃圾
He speaks beautifully
他说话很优美
If you don't want to hear more beautiful words, just leave
如果你不想听到更多美丽的话，就离开吧
Even if not, I'm still very angry today
就算不是，今天我也很生气
I want to take it easy today
今天我要轻松一点
You shoot first
你先开枪
Son, are you okay?
儿子，你还好吗？
Hey, boss, are you hurt somewhere?
嘿，头儿，你有什么地方受伤了吗？
This guy
这家伙
you are no longer friends
你们不再是朋友
Let's go, sun
我们走吧，太阳
try to die
尝试去死
ha
哈
I think I'm dead, what should I do?
我想我已经死了该怎么办
How to do it?
怎么做？
I have no idea
我不知道
hold on
坚持，稍等
I think I have a broken bone
我想我骨折了
(Li Jing'e, Li Zhouying)
（李景娥、李周英）
(Cause of death - cranial nerve compression asphyxia)
（死亡原因—— 脑神经受压窒息）
a bone is broken
一根骨头断了
Currently I am unable to do any form of bundling
目前，我无法进行任何形式的捆绑
please call my mom
请给我妈妈打电话
Mother
母亲
Let's go, Li Jing'e
走吧，李璟娥
Why did it really disappear?
为什么它真的就消失了？
- Wait until the police come - But
- 等到警察来 - 但是
Didn't you hear?
你没听见吗？
Can it really be left like this?
真的可以就这么放着吗？
drinking
饮酒
If something like this happens...
如果发生类似的事情..
It doesn't matter
没关系
Because I'm the only witness
因为我是唯一的见证人
I just saw you tweet
我刚刚看到你推
eyewitness?
目击者？
That's why I'm currently cautious
这就是为什么我目前持谨慎态度
He rarely drinks and comes home early
他很少喝酒 而且很早回家
If he is caught, he will have to pay a lot of money
如果他被抓住，他 将不得不支付很多钱
do you know?
你知道吗？
Yes
是的
I rarely drink
我很少喝酒
if you go home early
如果你提早回家
How can I see my parents' faces clearly?
我怎么能看清爸爸妈妈的脸色呢？
How can I look at my sister's face because I feel ashamed
我怎么能看着姐姐的脸因为我感到羞耻
Well
唔
I'm 22 and I'm sure there's nothing I can do
我已经22岁了， 我确信我无能为力
disappointing
令人失望
Are you a liar now?
你现在是骗子吗？
I no longer have the ability to live
我已经没有了生活的 能力
I'm exhausted
我累极了
I really can't stand it anymore
我实在是受不了了
Miss Korea...
韩国小姐..
Not really yet
还没有真正
But according to what I observed at the same time
但 根据我同时观察到的结果
Woo Jae Ri Geun Sun’s statement is roughly correct
宇在里根善的说法 大致正确
It's not bad to always dance in the club
总是在俱乐部跳舞 也不错
It's also great at making friends laugh
它也很擅长让朋友们开怀大笑
dress up
打扮
I have an eye for fashion
我有时尚眼光
Not Miss Korea, but many people on TV
不是韩国小姐，而是电视上的 很多人
If you know exactly what you want to do, you're around 22 years old
如果你明确知道自己想做什么，那么 你大约22岁
you can be young
你可以年轻
for real..
真正的..
Do you think so?
你这样认为吗？
this is not a lie
这不是谎言
How can someone who has been robbed of all their money be defrauded again?
钱被抢光的人 怎么可能再次被骗呢？
that money
那笔钱
This really doesn't allow this poor little boy to pay his tuition.
这实在是不给这个可怜的小男孩 交学费了
ha
哈
You didn't lie, did you?
你没说谎吧？
try to drink with everything
尝试用一切来喝
gentlemen
先生
Rob
抢
Well
唔
I took it back when I took it back unknowingly before.
之前不知不觉收回的时候 就收回了
my God
我的上帝
Mother
母亲
so so..
一般般..
Can I give it to grandma?
我可以送给奶奶吗？
What
什么
I can't go back
我无法回去
Hey, Lee Seung Yi
嘿，李升伊
- Do you know what happened today because of this - sister?
- 你知道今天因为这个而发生了什么吗 - 姐姐？
- Sister - Sorry, son E
- 姐姐 - 对不起，儿子E
I'm sorry for what I just said
我为我刚才所说的话感到抱歉
- I'm sorry - Sister
- 对不起 - 姐姐
i'm angry with you
我对你很生气
(Lee Hyoman)
（李孝满）
thank you for everything you did today
谢谢你今天所做的一切
Did not see the defendant
没有见到被告
I think I'm coming out of the fog a little now
我想我现在会稍微走出迷雾了
I don't know what went wrong again
我不知道又出了什么问题
Now there's only one chance left
现在只剩下一次机会了
But it's clear
但很 清楚
I am very satisfied with the scenery today
今天的景色让 我很满意
Hello
你好
Who are you?
你是谁？
teacher
老师
i believe in euben
我相信尤本
died
死了
he is dead sir
他死了，先生
it finally happened
它终于发生了
"A Stranger I Met"
《我遇见的一个陌生人》
How did it happen?
它是怎么发生的？
i have to explain
我必须解释一下
What you see is what you do
你所看到的就是你所做的
Explain everything from start to finish
从头到尾解释一切
You didn't go out, did you?
你没出去吧？
Time and place have changed, but death remains the same
时间和地点都变了，但 人的死却是一样的
I've never died in a place like this
我从来没有死在这样的地方
It all comes full circle and this is where we end up
一切又回到原点， 这就是我们结束的地方
This village is not human, why do you want to come here to die?
这个村子不是人， 为什么要来这里送死？
Why is it so stable?
为什么这么稳定？
Try to relax your face
尝试放松脸部
this is very obvious
这是非常明显的
"A Stranger I Met"
《我遇见的一个陌生人》